Tell me, Henry,
告訴我 Henry
why do you want to be Mr. Schmidt's assistant?
你為什麼想做Schmidt先生的助手?
He's my hero.
他是我的英雄
I know everything about him.
我對他瞭如指掌
"Possible stalker."
"可能是跟蹤狂"
And why do you think you're qualified?
你為什麼覺得能勝任這個工作?
Like him, I graduated high school at 16.
同他一樣 我16歲高中畢業
Then I completed the four-year computer science program
僅用兩年時間讀完了 哈佛四年制的計算機科學專業
during which, I founded an Internet startup,
其間 我建了個互聯網公司
and I'm currently two semesters shy of my law degree.
現在我再過倆學期就能拿到法律學位
So, "no law degree."
就是說 "沒有法律學位"
Let me tell you a few things
我來說說你可能不知道的 關於Walden Schmidt的二三事
Uh, the man is a genius.
那傢伙是個天才
I knew that.
我知道的
"Likes to interrupt."
"喜歡打斷別人說話"
He thinks in a different way than the rest of us.
他思考的方式同我們不一樣
His mind is always working.
他的大腦一直運轉
Every time he opens his mouth,
只要他一開口
it's because he has something important to say.
就是有重要的事要說
WALDEN: Love the new toilet paper
愛死你買的那個新廁紙了 Alan
It's like sliding down a rainbow.
跟溜彩虹滑梯似的
Except the pot at the end doesn't have any gold in it.
就是底下那個桶裡沒有金子 720p唳掛覃苺ㄩC.Ronaldo
When you hear something this good,
聽到如此至理名言
you should write it down.
你就應該記下來
I'm sorry.
不好意思
Who's this?
這是誰?
Oh, this is, uh, Henry Johnson.
哦 這是Henry Johnson
He's interviewing for the assistant job.
他是來應聘做助手的
Uh, assistant job?
助手?
Hi, Mr. Schmidt.
嗨 Schmidt先生
It's such an honor... (stuttering)
真是榮幸我能...
Eye contact.
禁止眼神接觸
It's okay, Henry.
沒事的 Henry
(mouthing)
[有事]
Alan, can I talk to you for a second.
Alan 能借一步說話嗎?
Uh, no problem, Mr. Schmidt.
沒問題 Schmidt先生
Tie? Really.
初次見面用"嗨" 有沒有搞錯
Not looking good, Hank.
前途不妙啊 Hank
What's up?
什麼事?
Why are you interviewing Henry to be my assistant
你為什麼要給Henry面試來當我助手?
when I just hired you to be my assistant?
我明明剛雇了你來當我助手
Oh, no, no, he's interviewing to be my assistant.
哦 不 不 他是來應聘當我助手的
Your assistant?
你的助手?
Well, intern, actually.
呃 準確來說 算實習生
He's not gonna cost us a penny, and he's gonna do
所以不用花我們一個字兒 他就能做完所有我不想做的卑賤活兒
Well, why don't I just hire him for free
那我為啥不直接免費雇了他 把中間人給踢掉?
And in case I'm going too fast, you're the middle man.
為防止你跟不上我速度 你就是那個中間人
But I'm the big picture guy.
但我是來掌控全局的
See, bringing Henry on to Team Schmidt...
懂沒? 讓Henry加入Schmidt之隊...
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Team Schmidt?
哇哦! Schmidt之隊?
Yeah, I'm gonna get hats and shirts made.
嗯 我還會去定做點帽子和T恤
Well, Henry is.
準確說 Henry會去的
We're gonna have a new slogan.
然後我們還會有新的口號
"No bull-Schmidt."
"不狗Schmidt(屎)"
"Schmidt happens."
"Schmidt(屎)事總會發生"
You're a Schmidt head.
你就是個Schmidt(屎)腦袋
I hired you to be my assistant to help you out financially
我是為幫你解決財務困難 才雇你做助手的
'cause you had close your chiropractic office.
因為你的按摩室關了門
I didn't have to close it; I'm in a rent dispute.
我其實不必關的 只是有些租務糾紛罷了
People in rent disputes don't fake their own death.
只是租務糾紛的人 不會去造自己死掉了的假
(doorbell rings) Oh, I'll get that.
我去開
You are looking good today, boss.
你今天氣色不錯 老闆
That's why he got good toilet paper.
所以他才能買到好廁紙
So my ass is clean while he's kissing it.
他親親我屁股 我屁股就乾淨了
Huh, my 12:00 must be early.
預約12點的人肯定是來早了
Someone who really wanted this job
真正想要這份工作的人
would've taken the initiative.
是會主動幹事的
Too late, Harvard.
太晚了 哈佛高材生
Hello.
你好
Hi. You Alan Harper?
嗨 你是Alan Harper?
Yes, I am. And, uh, and you are...?
對 是我 你是...?
Your niece.
你侄女
Eurniece?
Eurniece?
That's a... that's a pretty name.
真是個... 美麗的名字
Is that Dutch?
是荷蘭語嗎?
No, I'm Jenny.
不 我叫Jenny
I'm your brother Charlie's daughter.
我是你哥哥Charlie的女兒
Uh, Henry? Yes?
- 呃 Henry? - 在
Catch me.
接住我
♪ Two and a Half Men 11x01 ♪ Nangnangnangnang Original Air Date on September 26, 2013
-=伊甸園美劇論壇 http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- 榮譽出品 本字幕僅供學習交流，嚴禁用於商業途徑
== sync, corrected by elderman == @elder_man 720p版本调校：C.Ronaldo
-=YTET-伊甸園字幕組-歆組=- 翻譯: 霄霄 午桑 粒粒塵 校對: Baby 小貂 時間軸: Addic7ed
Uh, I'm-I'm sorry,
不 不好意思
did-did you say that you're... Charlie's daughter?
你剛剛說你是... Charlie的女兒?
Yeah.
是啊
Listen, I got a wicked hangover.
聽著 我剛宿醉得厲害
You got any aspirin, ibuprofen, rum, Scotch, tequila, vodka?
你有阿司匹林 布洛芬 朗姆 威士忌 龍舌蘭 伏特加不?
Uh, yeah, yeah, come on in.
有 有 進來吧
Uh, Henry, uh, get her an aspirin and vodka.
Henry 給她阿司匹林加伏特加
On it!
這就去!
Kitchen's that way. Damn it!
- 廚房在那邊 - 該死!
I-I can't believe this.
真是不敢相信
I mean, I can, but I-I can't.
我是說 我能相信 但我不敢相信
I mean, how did this happen?
我是說 怎麼會這樣的?
From what my mom told me...
據我媽說...
Ooh, can we... can we maybe turn down the lights?
你能... 你能把燈光調暗點嗎?
That's the sun.
那是太陽光
Right, I hate the sun.
是哦 我討厭太陽
It's like God calling you an alcoholic.
就像上帝說你是酒鬼似的
Anyway, according to my mom, it was love at first sight.
言歸正傳 根據我媽說的 他倆是一見鍾情
They met in a bar,
他們在酒吧遇見
they got drunk and had sex in the bathroom.
喝得大醉 在洗手間打了一炮
(chuckles) It was like a freakin' Disney movie.
跟特麼迪士尼電影似的
Poke-a-hot-ass.
戳屁股奇緣(Pocahontas/風中奇緣)
And where did the kid go for the vodka? Poland?
那小子跑哪兒去拿伏特加了? 波蘭嗎?
Look, I don't mean to be rude,
聽著 我不想無禮
but how do I know that you're really Charlie's daughter?
但我怎麼知道 你真是Charlie的女兒?
I mean, this could be some kind of scam.
這可能是個騙局啊
I have a picture of us together.
我有我倆的合照
It's in here somewhere.
在我手機裡
Oh, look. (laughs)
看啊
My vagina.
我的小陰陰
Oh, wait, that's not mine.
喔 等等 不是我的誒!
Oh, that's mine.
這張才是我的
Ah, there you go.
啊 找到了
This was taken at my fourth birthday party.
這是我四歲生日時照的
Just a heads up, I might vomit; where's the nearest bathroom?
提醒一下 我可能要吐了 最近的洗手間在哪兒?
Oh, right down the hall.
走廊盡頭就是
Okay, I think we're good,
行 我覺得現在應該不會吐
but it's always nice to have a plan.
但有準備總是好的
Anyway, this was party was the last time I saw him.
話說回來 那次派對是我最後一次見他
After that, he just sent checks.
那之後 他就只寄支票了
He-he sent checks?
他 他寄支票了?
Yeah, my mom didn't want him to have anything to do with me,
嗯 我媽媽不希望他對我有任何影響
but he always made sure I was taken care of.
但他總是保證我得到好的照顧
He never said a word about any of this to me.
這整件事他對我隻字未提
I'm his brother, his-his blood.
我是他弟弟 親弟弟
Were they big checks?
是大額支票嗎?
Yeah, got one every month.
嗯 每月都寄
Bastard.
混蛋
My mom just called me special.
我媽就只叫我"特殊兒童"
This Henry guy is awesome.
那個叫Henry的傢伙酷斃了
Did you know I won a spelling bee in fifth grade?
你知道我五年級時贏過拼字大賽嗎?
I didn't!
我自己都不知道!
Who's this, Henry's assistant?
這是誰 Henry的助手?
Walden, this is Jenny,
Walden 這是Jenny
my brother's daughter.
我哥哥的女兒
Really?
是嗎?
Hi.
- 嗨
I, uh, didn't know Charlie had a daughter.
我都不知道Charlie還有個女兒
Neither did I.
我原先也不知道
He sent her checks, big checks.
他還給她寄支票 大額支票
Not that that matters now.
不過現在也不重要了
(whispers): Every month!
每個月啊!
Hey, am I related
嗨 我和這個
to Abercrombie & Fitch over here?
A&F陽光帥小伙有血緣關係嗎?
No, I own the house.
不 我是房子的主人
Oh. I assumed it was Alan's.
我還以為這是Alan的房子
So does he.
他也這麼以為
So, uh, tell us more about you.
那 再給我們說說你的情況
Not much to tell.
沒多少可說的
I was born in New York,
我生在紐約
got kicked out of a few private schools,
被好幾所私立學校退學
tried to become a doctor to make my mom happy,
為了討老媽開心 想試著學醫
dropped out, became an actress to piss her off.
退學 成了演員 來氣老媽
An actress, oh.
演員啊
Your father loved actresses.
你父親可喜愛演員了
Yeah, I was only going to med school
是啊 我上醫學院就是為了
so I could write myself prescriptions for oxy.
能給自己開羥考酮的處方
Oh, your father loved oxy.
你父親愛死羥考酮了
HENRY: Sorry it took so long.
不好意思久等了
Here's vodka and two aspirin.
你要的伏特加和兩片阿司匹林
Thank God. Oh.
謝天謝地
I was wrong; I am gonna puke.
我錯了 我得去吐了
Your father loved to puke.
你父親老愛吐了
So, when I was, like, five,
我差不多5歲時
my mom married this total loser named Rob.
我媽跟一個叫Rob的蠢蛋結婚了
He moved in with us and never looked for a job,
他搬過來跟我們住 從沒出去找過工作
but he's been sponging off of her ever since.
就此賴著她生活
Who does that?
誰還會幹這種事?
So, uh, how long you been in L.A.?
你在洛杉磯多久了?
Couple weeks.
幾周
And you got a place to stay?
有地方住嗎?
He asks, knowing full well she's a Harper.
雖然知道她姓Harper 他還是這麼問了
Yeah, I'm crashing at a friend's house.
有啊 借住在朋友家
That's great. Friends are great.
那很好 朋友最好了
You should make some friends, Alan.
你應該交些朋友 Alan
So, just the two of you live here?
只有你們倆住在這?
Uh, well, my son, your cousin Jake,
還有我兒子 你的堂弟Jake
uh, used to live with us, but he's in the army now.
以前和我們住一起 但現在去參軍了
Stationed in Japan.
駐紮在日本
Oh, that's impressive.
很厲害啊
Because of the time difference,
因為時差的關係
he thinks he lives in the future.
他覺得自己生活在未來世界
Maybe we can call him and find out
我們可以打電話問問他
when this headache's gonna go away.
我的頭疼啥時候能好
Oh, and, uh, you have a grandmother.
你還有個奶奶
Oh, that's great!
那太好了!
In theory.
名義上的
When she finds out she has a granddaughter,
當她發現她有個孫女 會心臟病發的
You know, I'm gonna call her right now.
我現在就去打給她
This is it.
就是這兒了
This was your dad's room.
這以前是你爸爸的房間
Wow.
哇
I always tried to imagine what my dad's life was like.
我總是想像爸爸的生活是什麼樣
It's weird to finally see it.
終於親眼見到了 感覺又很怪
I never met him, but I heard he was quite a guy.
我沒見過他 但聽說他很獨特
I heard he was a drunken man whore.
我聽說他是個酗酒的淫蕩男
Like I said, quite a guy.
如我所說 很獨特
So, uh,
那麼
this your and Alan's room?
這是你和Alan的房間嗎?
What?
什麼?
(chuckles): No.
當然不是
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
不是 不是
We're not... I'm not...
我們不是 我不是...
The, um... really?
真的嗎?
You really don't think I can do better than Alan?
你真覺得 我只能找Alan那種水準的?
I don't know.
我不知道
Maybe he's got a huge schlong.
可能他的雞雞很大呢
Well, we're not a couple, and he doesn't.
我們不是好基友 他的也沒那麼大
Which is fine. I mean, not that size matters.
也還行吧 我是說 尺寸不重要
Not that I was looking.
我沒有故意盯著看的
I'm not gay.
我不是基
So why is he still living here?
那為什麼他還住這裡?
Well, at first...
起初呢
Then...
接著呢...
I don't know.
我也不知道
this is where your dad used to sleep.
這是你爸爸以前的臥室
I got a new mattress,
我換了新床墊
and I replaced the carpets and the drapes
還換了地毯和窗簾
and pretty much anything that could absorb fluid.
更換了所有會吸收液體的東西
Wow.
不錯
If these walls could talk.
真希望這些牆壁能說話
They'd probably say, "Can I get a towel?"
他們可能會說 "能給我塊毛巾嗎?"
So, I mean,
我是說
I wish there was more that Charlie left behind.
我希望Charlie能留下了更多東西 除了Alan的話
So... (sighs)
所以呢
my dad stood in this same spot, staring out at the ocean.
我的爸爸以前就站在這個位置 凝視著大海
I wonder what was going through his mind.
我想知道他那時腦子都有啥
I wonder what he was thinking.
想知道他當時在想啥
Besides, of course,
當然除了 "我怎樣能把 這倆性感的衝浪小妞給睡了?" 之外
Huh, now I'm thinking it.
我現在也在想這個了
Oh, please.
別鬧
With your looks and this house, I'm sure you do fine.
憑你的長相和這幢房子 肯定可以的
Well, you'd think that, but the truth is,
你可能這麼認為 但事實是
when it comes to women, I've never really been much
關於女人的問題
of a casual sex kind of guy.
我從來不亂來的
And every time I do get close to one,
每當我和一個女人越來越親近
she ends up pulling away from me,
她總會離我而去
and then I wind up back in this room,
最後我總回到這間房
thinking where I went wrong again.
思考我又哪裡錯了
Alone.
獨自一人
So alone.
好孤獨的
Oh, yeah.
是了
(chuckles) You're not gay.
你肯定不是基
Mom, I have some news for you.
媽 我有個消息告訴你
Sit down.
你先坐下
Okay, push him off and sit up.
把他推開 坐起來
Um, I know this is gonna come as quite the shock,
我知道這很突然
but it turns out Charlie has a daughter.
但原來Charlie有個女兒
Mom? Mom?
媽媽? 媽媽?
Are you dead?
你死了嗎?
Oh, good.
噢太好了
Um, no, I know.
不是 我知道
I know, it's crazy, right?
太瘋狂了 對吧?
Yeah, no, she's here now.
不 她現在就在這裡
Well, well, come on over.
好吧 過來吧
Okay, finish first and then come over.
好吧 先做完再過來
Good news. Uh, my mother's on her way over.
好消息 我母親要過來了
First time I've ever said that.
還是頭一次說這話
Wow, insta-family.
速成家庭啊
Uncle, grandmother,
叔叔 奶奶
step-hot-guy.
繼帥哥
I'm sorry, I don't know what to call you.
對不起 我不知道你叫啥
Oh, step-hot-guy works.
繼帥哥挺好的
All that's missing is my dad.
只缺我爸爸了
Actually, he's here, too.
事實上 他也在這裡的
Um, follow me.
跟我來
Uh, where are we going?
我們去哪?
Uh, well, you know how sailors get buried at sea?
你知道水手是被海葬吧?
Yeah.
是的
I keep Charlie in the liquor cabinet.
我把Charlie安置在酒櫃裡了
Let's see.
我們去看看
Uh, Johnnie Walker, Jack Daniel's...
傑克丹尼 尊尼獲加...
Charlie Harper.
Charlie Harper
Huh, he looks different than his pictures.
他本人和照片看起來不一樣啊
Um, Charlie, this is your daughter Jenny.
Charlie 這是你女兒Jenny
Hi, Dad!
你好啊 爸爸!
This seems weird. Does this seem weird to anybody else?
這樣有點詭異 你們有覺得嗎?
Yes, it's weird.
是的 很詭異
Almost as weird as when we take him to the movies.
差不多和我們帶他去看電影一樣詭異
Charlie, I wish you were here
Charlie 真希望你還健在
to see how beautiful your daughter turned out.
能看到你閨女出落得多麼美麗
I-I think you'd be impressed.
我想你會大吃一驚的
I think a lot of...
我想很多人都會...
Oh!
噢!
Oh, not again.
又來?
I ain't cleaning that up.
我是不掃的
Oh. Oh, look.
瞧
A quarter.
25分錢
Unbelievable.
難以置信
You even mooch off the dead.
你居然黑死人的錢
One more.
再來一杯
Yeah, you're Charlie's daughter.
沒錯 你肯定是Charlie的女兒
You don't seem very surprised.
你看來並不吃驚啊
Only surprised there aren't more of you running around.
我吃驚的是沒更多私生子女上門
God, I loved your dad.
天吶 我愛你爸爸
I remember the first time I met him.
我記得第一次見他時
He asked me if I knew how to do three things:
他問我是否會做三件事:
cook, clean and score an eight ball
煮飯 打掃和凌晨2點半買到毒品
I told him I didn't know how to cook or clean.
我告訴他我不會煮飯打掃
I've been here ever since.
然後就一直做到今天
I'm-I'm sure you have a story about Charlie
你一定知道一些關於Charlie 不涉及毒品的事的
Okay. One time at Mardi Gras...
好吧 有一次狂歡節...
Or alcohol.
也不涉及酒精
All right.
好吧
Once when Charlie was in Vegas...
有回Charlie在拉斯維加斯...
Or hookers.
也不涉及妓女
Geez, you're really tying my hands!
天吶 我都沒東西好講了!
Okay, I got it.
好吧 我知道了
It was New Year's Eve,
在新年前夜
and Charlie was super not drunk,
Charlie一點沒醉
and he was with this crazy not hooker,
和他非妓女的瘋女友在一起
and he decided to have his sphincter bleached.
去漂白他的括約肌(有興趣知道自行谷歌咳)
Whoa! Whoa! What?
等下 什麼?
Why?
為什麼?
Because he cared about women.
因為他關愛女性啊
Unfortunately, it got infected, and he needed me
很不幸的 被感染了 他需要我幫他抹點軟膏
I'm sorry.
很抱歉
It's just that I miss him so much!
只是我實在太想他了!
God took the wrong Harper!
老天爺錯收了哥哥去!
EVELYN: Where is my granddaughter?
我的孫女在哪?
Did it just get cold in here?
這裡是不是突然變冷了?
Oh, my God.
我的天哪
Look at you.
看看你
Mom, this is Jenny.
媽媽 這是Jenny
Jenny,
Jenny
this is Evelyn.
這位是Evelyn
You are so beautiful.
你好漂亮
You remind me of me ten years ago.
你讓我想起十年前的自己
Your father was the apple of my eye.
你父親是我的掌上明珠
My greatest gift.
我最好的禮物
My reason for living.
我活下去的動力
Uh, hello.
喂
Hello, Alan.
你好Alan
I can't believe I finally have a grandchild.
不敢相信我終於有孫輩了!
You already have a grandchild-- Jake.
你一直都有啊 Jake不是嗎
Oh. Sure. Yeah.
哦 當然了
So, Jennifer...
那 Jennifer...
Actually, it's Jenny.
其實是Jenny
Darling, you're not 12 anymore. It's Jennifer.
寶貝 你不是小孩了 是Jennifer
We are going to have so much fun together:
我們會相處得很愉快的
lunching, shopping, taking care of those eyebrows.
午餐 購物 帶你去修眉毛
Where are you staying while you're in town?
你來這住哪兒?
I'm crashing on a friend's couch.
在我朋友沙發上擠擠
Not anymore. You'll stay with me.
別再去了 過來和我住
Aw! I love you, Evelyn.
我愛你 Evelyn
Whoa, whoa! If she's staying anywhere,
喂!
she's gonna stay at my place.
她要住也是住我這
And by "your place," do you mean
你說的 "我這" 是指
the office that you stopped paying rent at
你交不起租金的辦公室
or the house that you've never paid rent at?
還是從不交租金的住處?
Look, I'm not gonna let my mom screw her up
我不能讓我媽帶壞她
like she did me and Charlie.
像帶壞我和Charlie一樣
Hey! I was a good mother.
嘿! 我是個好母親
No, you know who was a good mother?
不 你知道誰是好母親嗎?
Our housekeeper Adela. She even breast-fed me.
我們的管家Adela 她甚至用母乳餵我
She had just had a baby.
她剛生完小孩
And when the milk truck is parked on the street,
送奶車都停家門口了
you don't go to the grocery store.
誰還去雜貨店買牛奶
Besides, you-you used to gnaw on me.
而且你總是舔我
You're gnawer.
你個舔人鬼
Nang-nang-nang-nang- nang-nang-nang.
喃喃喃喃喃喃喃
You know what? She's gonna stay in Jake's room.
她住Jake的房間
Whoa, whoa, no.
等等 不
I do not want Jake's room to become Jenny's room.
我不想Jake的房間變成Jenny的房間
You know, in fact, there is no Jake's room
實際上壓根沒有Jake的房間
and there's no Jenny's room.
也沒有Jenny的房間
There's just Walden's room.
只有Walden的房間
And Charlie's room.
和Charlie的房間
Why don't we let her decide?
我們不如讓她自己決定?
Yeah, yeah, it's up to her.
是是 聽她的
Is anyone listening to me?!
就沒人聽我的嗎?!
Jennifer?
Jennifer?
Where'd she go?
她去哪兒了?
Nice job, Alan.
做得好 Alan
You made another woman disappear.
又一個女人因為你消失了
Can you believe her?
難以置信吧?
What did I do to her to make her hate me so much?
我到底做了什麼讓她這麼恨我?
Nang-nang-nang-nang- nang-nang-nang.
喃喃喃喃喃喃喃
Oh, oh. What, you, too?
什麼 你也這樣?
Oh!
哦!
Son of a...
臥槽你...
Ooh, a nickel!
5美分!
This is ridiculous.
太荒謬了
We're never going to find her.
我們再也找不到她了
I don't understand why she ran off like that.
我不明白她為什麼跑掉
I can think of two reasons.
我能想到兩個原因
First I lost my Charlie, now I've lost my Jennifer.
先是失去了我的Charlie 現在又失去了Jennifer
You still have your Alan.
你還有你的Alan
Oh! Don't make it worse.
哦! 別再添堵了
Nang-nang-nang-nang- nang-nang-nang.
喃喃喃喃喃喃喃
Oh, God, my granddaughter's gone forever.
天 我的孫女就此離開了
Oh, there she is at the bus stop.
她在公交站呢
Oh, God, my granddaughter rides the bus!
天 我孫女居然坐公汽!
Jenny, what are you doing?
Jenny 你幹嘛呢?
I'm trying to get away from you people.
我要離開你們這些人
Look, I just wanted to see where my dad lived.
我只想看看我爸住哪兒
I didn't want to screw up your family.
我不想搞砸你們的關係
Uh, for the record,
確切地說
they were screwed up long before you got here.
他倆在你來之前很久前就已經搞砸了
It's true.
是真的
H-Hey, if I'm screwed up, it's your fault.
嘿 如果我搞砸 那也是你的錯
You raised me.
我是你養大的
I didn't raise you, Adela did.
養大你的不是我 是Adela
Look, I already have a messed-up family.
我已經有個一團糟的家了
I-I don't need another one.
不想再招惹一個
Oh, we're sorry.
不好意思
This is just how we express our love.
這是我們表達愛意的方式
Through hate. Oh, no, no, no.
- 通過厭惡 - 不不不
W-We don't hate each other.
我們並非彼此憎惡
I mean, the truth is, my mother is an amazing woman.
事實上 我母親是位了不起的女人
I mean, she-she raised two kids on her own,
她獨自撫養兩個孩子
she's a successful businesswoman,
還是位成功的女商人
she has impeccable taste.
有無懈可擊的品味
Thank you, Alan.
謝謝你 Alan
Oh, right.
啊 對
Uh, and Alan is...
Alan呢 是...
the reason I had my tubes tied.
我做結紮手術的原因
Because she knew she would never do better than me.
因為她知道她生不出比我更好的小孩了
Please, sweetheart, I just found you.
拜託 寶貝兒 我剛認回你
I can't lose you now.
不能再次失去你了
We want you to be a part of our lives.
我們想你融入我們的生活
What do you say?
可以嗎?
Well, if I'm gonna be a part of this family,
要成為這個家庭一員
I'm gonna need a drink.
我得先喝一杯
You hear that, Charlie?
聽到了嗎 Charlie?
Your daughter needs a drink.
你女兒需要喝一杯
You're looking the wrong way, Mom.
看錯方向了 老媽
A toast. To Charlie Harper.
敬Charlie Harper
My brother, your son, your father, and your...
我的哥哥 你的兒子 你的父親 你的...
Guy who got hit by a train so I could buy his beach house?
被火車撞死的前屋主?
Sorry, Evelyn.
抱歉 Evelyn
It's okay. I got the commission.
沒事 我賺到了佣金
To Charlie.
敬Charlie
So, is that the bathroom
那個洗手間就是孕育出我的地方?
It is.
是的
Want to see it?
想看看不?
I do.
想
Text a picture of it to my mom.
拍張照發給我媽
Should be good for some guilt money.
可以換點錢來花花
I'll run interference.
我來開路
All right, everybody out!
各位請出來!
Woman visiting the place of her conception!
姑娘要參觀她的孕育之地!
I can't tell you how relieved I am
終於後繼有人
to finally have an heir. Mm.
- 我總算能鬆口氣了 - 唔
Wait, what?
等下 什麼?
She's my granddaughter.
她是我的孫女
I want to provide for her.
我想供養她
And since I wasn't around
既然過去這25年 我沒能盡到這個義務
it's only fitting that she inherit my estate.
那就讓她繼承我的財產吧
You weren't around for the first 45 years of my life.
這45年 你也沒盡供養我的義務
You have Walden!
你有Walden!
Oh, oh, do I? Do you see a ring on this finger?
哦 是嗎? 我無名指上戴婚戒了?
Don't worry, darling.
別擔心 親愛的
There's a little something for you in my will.
我遺囑上有留給你一點
A little something?
一點?
Look, if you knew
你要是知道
you were gonna get everything,
你會繼承一切
you would've smothered me with a pillow years ago.
多年前就拿枕頭悶死我了
That is not true.
並非如此
If I knew I had money coming, I'd hire a professional.
如果知道有錢入賬 我會雇個專業人士
How'd it go? Great.
- 如何? - 很棒
I laughed, I cried.
我笑過 哭過
I peed.
我尿過
How are you guys doing over here?
怎麼樣?
Can I get you anything else?
有什麼需要嗎?
Yeah, we might need a designated driver
我們需要一名代駕
to get us back to his beautiful beach house.
載我們回他漂亮的海濱別墅
I'll take you guys. I get off in 15.
我載你們 我15分鐘後下班
Great. Thanks.
太好了 謝謝
She's cute.
她很可愛
Told ya.
我說吧
Malibu beach house gets you laid every time.
利用馬裡布海景房泡妞屢試不爽
Not every time.
也不能說屢次
Oh, my God, this house is amazing!
天 這屋子碉堡了!
Well, it's... Yeah.
這個... 是啊
And look at that view.
你看這景致
It's even better from the bedroom.
臥室的景觀還要好
Want to see?
想看不?
Yeah.
想
After you.
樓上請
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
等等等等
Where are you going?
你去哪兒?
Up to show her.
帶她看看
Oh, you thought...?
哦 你以為...?
Oh, no-no-no-no-no, she's mine.
不不不不不 她是我的
Next time I'll get two.
下次我帶倆來
What just happened?
剛什麼情況?
Charlie's back.
Charlie回歸了
Good morning.
早上好
No, no, not good.
不 不好
I slept in the guest room of my own house,
我得睡自家的客房
and I'm pretty sure I still have some of your brother in my ear.
而且耳朵裡好像有你哥骨灰
Don't worry, tonight I'll tell Jenny
別擔心 今晚我會告訴Jenny
that your bedroom's off limits.
你臥室是禁地
No, there is no tonight!
不 沒有今晚了!
But she's family.
但她是家人
Not my family.
不是我家人
And I'm gonna tell her she can't stay.
我要去告訴她 她不能住在這
Morning. Hi.
- 早 - 嗨
You girls have a good night?
昨晚過得好嗎?
Oh, yeah.
相當
I'm surprised I can even talk.
我居然還能張口說話
You were saying? Shut up.
- 你剛說啥來著? - 閉嘴
== sync, corrected by elderman == @elder_man 720p版本调校：C.Ronaldo
-------------------------- 本論壇字幕僅翻譯交流學習之用 禁止任何商業用途否則後果自負 -------------------------- 720p唳掛覃苺ㄩC.Ronaldo